I've never made her is eggs
我从来没有做过炒鸡蛋
I can definitely scrambled
我绝对可以炒
I just heard eating eggs a year ago
我一年前才听说吃鸡蛋
I forgot to do
我忘了做
Square one
一号广场
Cold break
寒假
York
纽约
Maybe I'll do a little salt
也许我会加一点盐
Westborough ma
I like to go by the time you poured on those national sizzle happening
我喜欢在您倾倒那些全国性的混乱时去
My boyfriend's going to see this since I was so embarrassed
我好不好意思我男朋友要去看
Scrambled eggs coming up
炒鸡蛋来了
Tractor boy
拖拉机男孩
The number for the amount of times that I need
我需要的次数
Jeremy
You got a salty taste like my mum's legs
你像我妈妈的腿一样咸
This bad boy
这个坏男孩
Opinion
意见
That carries flavour
带有味道
I know that they're ready to hit the pen when they're all Incorporated
我知道他们都准备成立时已经准备好了
I'm looking for them to not look to drive and also not look like
我正在寻找他们不要开车也不喜欢
I like when it's not too cooked
我喜欢不太熟的时候
It's a pretty simple task to improve the quality of your scrambled eggs
改善炒鸡蛋的质量是一项非常简单的任务
Where is break the eggs
鸡蛋在哪里破
Always on a flat surface
始终在平坦的表面上
No wish would be fine here 1/4 is fine as well
没关系就好了1/4也好
I know these are ready when basically when I stop staring for not seeing you lumps or clumps of either dry or egg
我知道这些基本上已经准备好了，基本上当我停止注视时看不到您的块状或块状的干或鸡蛋
What are my eggs before they go into the pan
脂肪下面我的鸡蛋是什么
So when were scrambling eggs the really important thing is that you just had some type of fat in the pan
因此，当您在加鸡蛋时，最重要的是锅里只有一些脂肪
Can getting a nice evening coding so my ex girl
可以得到一个不错的晚上编码，所以我的前女友
Allowed sizzle when you add eggs to the pan for scrambled eggs
将鸡蛋加到平底锅里炒鸡蛋时允许嘶嘶声
Am I cooking time music
我在煮时间音乐吗
I'm actually gonna turn the burner off right before they're ready and just use the residual heat the pan I want these eggs
我实际上是要在准备好之前关闭燃烧器，然后用锅里的余热我要这些鸡蛋
Basically I would have custody which means there's a bit of slightly runny egg
基本上我会有监护权，这意味着鸡蛋有点“流鼻涕”
16 in between and that we're all looking for a proper scrambled egg
介于两者之间，我们都在寻找适当的炒鸡蛋